SUNDAY 7:30 A.M.
Alex?
All's quiet. Come on in.
- OK, thanks.
OK, you know the order.
Stay focussed.
Right. We've got
100 minutes from now.
Stop, stop.
OK, go.
Headlamps off.
81 minutes left.
35.
Ready.
420.
312.
- Ready.
456.
Ready.
151.
We said no stocks and bonds.
Just cash and jewellery.
Fuck! We can't leave all this loot!
- You're done. Move.
31 minutes left.
Get the syringe with novocaine.
Come on.
Get him out of here.
Let's go.
We've got six minutes left.
Come on. Move it!
Fuckin' hell, we did it!
EEN AND SKYLINE ENTERTAINMENT
PRESENT
WITH THE SUPPORT OF
THE FLANDERS
AUDIOVISUAL FUND / MEDIA FUND
No, there's too much. I'm sorry.
I can't take everything,
it's out of the question.
So make me an offer.
- Make you an offer? OK. I'll...
I'll just take the diamonds.
And the necklaces.
And I suggest you smelt the gold and
come back and see me in December.
You only want cash.
I can't have any for you before then.
How much?
600,000 euro. In cash.
That's all I can give you at the moment.
That's 24 million old Belgian francs.
I think it's a fair offer.
Given the circumstances.
OK, I accept.
OK.
Was there something else?
No. No, no. Take it. I...
I just thought that maybe you could...
I thought about that too.
No one would know.
MONDAY 8:00 A.M.
Morning, Sylvia.
- Good morning, Mr Robijns.
Good weekend? I was stuck in traffic for
an hour, make my coffee extra strong.
Your mail, Mr Robijns.
- I'll just turn the alarm off first.
Fuck!
Christ!
Oh, fuck!
Jesus Christ!
The stocks and bonds are still there.
- Yes.
I can see that too.
How many safes have been opened?
- 66.
Bloody hell! I was afraid of that.
Shit!
It would have to be
the 66 sensitive safes.
Mr Jonkhere...
shouldn't we call the police?
Let me think.
Did Sylvia notice anything?
- No.
Did you tell her anything?
Send her home.
What? Sylvia is the first person
the police will want to question.
There won't be any police.
D'you think this is a coincidence?
All that work. Just for those 66 safes.
No one else is coming in here today.
Think of an excuse.
The computer's crashed, for example.
By this evening
I want a list of all personnel
who know the identity of
the safes' owners.
There's a traitor in our midst.
A spy.
There has to be.
Bye, Mr Robijns.
- See you tomorrow, Sylvia.
Can you put the bins out, sweetheart?
And the shopping list is on the fridge.
Don't spoil my day off.
- Come on, I have to go to work.
I worked 32 hours this weekend.
- I know, darling.